orbs.com 2013-08-06

# Orbs.com Website Builder

## Privacy Policy

Last updated: June 21, 2010 

Orbs.com is committed to protecting your personal information ("Personal Data"). This privacy policy details what information Orbs.com collects, how it's collected and what restrictions there are on sharing it. 

### What Personal Information We Collect

When you sign up for a Orbs.com account, we collect personal information about you including your name and e-mail address. We use such information to provide the service you requested, to monitor internal usage of our Site, and to contact you from time to time about us, our Site, and our products and services. 

Please note that we are not responsible for any personal information that you voluntarily provide through edits and submissions on any Orbs.com Site. This includes your user name and your user profile information if you've opted to make it public. 

If you send a communication to Orbs.com, we may hold onto that communication so that we can respond appropriately, track issues and use your feedback to improve our service. 

### What Information is Automatically Collected

When you visit our Site, some information is also automatically collected. For example, your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and the time and date of your visit and Site pages visited. This information helps us to optimize our Sites and improve our services to you. 

We also use "cookies" which are small files that are sent from a web server to your browser and then stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are used to keep you logged into your Site while you make changes to it. They may also be used to remember your preferences. Please note that if you set your browser to not accept cookies, certain areas of our Site may not function properly. 

### Restrictions on Sharing Personal Information

We do not sell, rent or share personal information with third parties without your prior consent except in these limited circumstances: 

**Aggregated Data** \- We may from time to time, combine data from a group of users but remove all personal identifying information about individual users. This aggregate information helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new services and improve existing services to customers. We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of Orbs.com with certain restrictions. 

**Service Providers** \- We may enter into a relationship with a third party who provides services to us (e.g. data storage services, data management). In those circumstances, we disclose information about you that is necessary for such service providers to perform those services, but only if such service providers agree not to disclose your information except as necessary to perform their services. 

**Other Circumstances** \- Notwithstanding anything in this privacy policy to the contrary, we reserve the right, unless limited by applicable law, to share any information we have collected about you or that you have submitted: (1) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes, or to establish, protect, or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (2) if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or property; (3) if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding situations that involve significant abuse of our website infrastructure or the Internet in general (such as voluminous spamming, denial of service attacks, or attempts to compromise the security of information); (4) to our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us (in which case we will require such entities to honor this privacy policy); and (5) if we are acquired by or merged with another entity. 

### Securing Your Personal Information

We have taken reasonable security measures to safeguard your personal information while it is under our control. However, you are responsible for keeping your password confidential and not disclosing it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of our Site by any person using your password. If you find your password or account is being used by someone without your consent, or you discover any other breach of security, you agree to notify us immediately at [policyhelp@orbs.com](mailto:policyhelp@orbs.com). 

While we do our utmost to safeguard your information, please remember that privacy over the Internet cannot be guaranteed, and keep this in mind when deciding what information to transmit or broadcast through your Site. 

### Policy Changes

We may update this privacy policy from time to time as our privacy practices keep up to date with technology and legal developments. We will notify you of changes by posting the new policy on our Sites and indicating at the top of our privacy policy the date it was last updated. You are encouraged to review our privacy policy regularly to check for any changes. 

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us at [policyhelp@orbs.com](mailto:policyhelp@orbs.com).
